<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Ovaries</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ovaryres">My Ovaries</string>
    <string name="empty"></string>
    <string name="age">Personal Details</string>
    <string name="medic">Medical Details</string>
    <string name="howold">Age</string>
    <string name="required">(required)</string>
    <string name="iam">I am\u0020</string>
    <string name="and">\u0020and\u0020</string>
    <string name="years">years,</string>
    <string name="months">months.</string>
    <string name="leftov">Left Ovary</string>
    <string name="rightov">Right Ovary</string>
    <string name="firstuse">Configuring app for first time use. Please wait....</string>
    <string name="firstusetitle">App Configuration</string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright ©\u0020</string>
    <string name="name">Olalekan Baruwa.\u0020</string>
    <string name="allrights">All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight:\u0020</string>
    <string name="weighthint">Your Weight</string>
    <string name="height">Height:\u0020</string>
    <string name="chooseheight">Your Height</string>
    <string name="body">Body</string>
    <string name="fromblood">Blood Test Results (if known)</string>
    <string name="fromultrasound">Ultrasound Results (if known)</string>
    <string name="genetics2">Genetics</string>
    <string name="periods">Do you have regular periods?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="overall">Overall Advice</string>
    <string name="history">Usage History</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="pcalc">Personalized Calculator</string>
    <string name="nousage">No usage history available.</string>
    <string name="web">Web</string>
    <string name="ageerrortitle">Error</string>
    <string name="ageerror">Your age is required before you can proceed. (Choose your birth year and month)</string>
    <string name="todo">What would you like to do?</string>
    <string name="view">View</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="goback">Go back</string>
    <string name="delItem">Are you sure you want to delete this item?</string>
    <string name="resnotavail">N/A</string>
    <string name="resnotavailfull">Results not available for specified age.</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    
    <string name="menopause">"Your Mother's Age at Menopause (if known)"</string>
    <string name="menopause2">"Mother's Age at Menopause"</string>
    <string name="mage">"Mother's age"</string>
    <string name="mmagevaluetext">"There is substantial evidence that genetic factors play a major role in determining a woman’s age at menopause. 
        It is likely that this influence is exerted through an effect on ovarian reserve. 
        One of the most frequently studied areas is the association between mothers’ and daughters’ ages at menopause. 
        Since mothers and daughters share 50% of their genes, if age at menopause is affected by genetic factors, 
        it is likely that a significant correlation would exist between mothers’ and daughters’ ages at menopause. Based on the research in this \u0020"</string>
    <string name="mmagevaluetext2">the heritability of menopausal age was 44%, which is quite significant in knowing the ovarian reserve levels.</string>    
    
    <string name="amh">AMH value.</string>
    <string name="amhvalue">AMH Value (ng/L or pm/L)</string>
    <string name="amhhint">Your AMH value</string>
    <string name="amhvaluetext">Anti-Mullerian Hormone value is derived from undergoing a blood test. AMH is a natural protein that plays a 
        major role in the development of the primary ovarian follicles. Research has shown that there is a significant correlation between serum AMH and the number of follicles in the ovaries. Therefore, 
        it is an important part of the predictive measures of the ovarian reserve levels in humans. It is important to note that the AMH value peaks at approximately the age of 25.</string>
    
    <string name="fsh">FSH value.</string>
    <string name="fshvalue">FSH Value (mLU/mL)</string>
    <string name="fshhint">Your FSH value</string>
    <string name="fshvaluetext">Follicle-stimulating Hormone (FSH) is a hormone that stimulates the growth of egg follicles, therefore it plays a vital role in helping to determine the ovarian reserve.</string>
    
    <string name="vol">ovarian volume.</string>
    <string name="volvalue">Ovarian Volume (mL)</string>
    <string name="volhint">Enter volume</string>
    <string name="volvaluetext">"Ovarian volume is a calculation/measurement of the length, width, and depth of each of the ovaries. Medical studies have correlated ovarian size with a woman's ability to respond adequately to fertility medications."</string>
    
    <string name="afc">antral-follicle count.</string>
    <string name="afcvalue">Antral-Follicle Count</string>
    <string name="afchint">Enter AFC value</string>
    <string name="afcvaluetext">"Antral-Follicle count (AFC) is a value that can be determined from a trans-vaginal ultrasound scan, it is the number of antral follicles on both ovaries. In determining the ovarian reserve level, AFC is a major determinant because is gives a fairly accurate number of eggs (oocytes) remaining in the ovaries."</string>
    
    <string name="ngfvalue">Your remaining Ovarian Reserve</string>
    <string name="ngfvaluetext">"The cells that can become eggs are called non-growing follicles (<b>NGFs</b> for short). You were born with a fixed number of NGFs in your ovaries, this is your <b>Ovarian Reserve</b>. Typically there are about 400,000 in each ovary, but there is a large amount of variation so you could have been born with between 70,000 and 3 million NGFs.
        <br />
        There is a cycle that recruits some NGFs which grow into bigger and bigger follicles, but most of them die during the cycle. Only very few (about 400 for your whole reproductive lifespan) turn into eggs that can be fertilized.
        <br />
        It is believed that women who start with a high Ovarian Reserve lose NGFs quickly and women who have a low Ovarian Reserve lose NGFs slowly. This is because menopause happens for all women when there are about 1,000 NGFs left at an average age of 51 years.
        <br />
        This enables us to estimate the percentage of NGFs remaining for a woman of any age. The estimates are based on the Wallace-Kelsey model of NGF populations throughout life. Click on the link below to read the <b>Science behind your results</b>:\u0020"</string>
    
    <string name="smokingtext">"Smoking is linked to an earlier menopause, because in late reproductive age women at a given time, smokers are more likely to be menopausal than non-smokers. 
        Research has shown that women who smoke more often than not reach the menopausal age earlier that non-smokers."</string>
    
    <string name="bmivaluetext">There is currently no concrete evidence that a high BMI will result in an adverse effect on the ovarian reserve.</string>
    
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="info">Information</string>
    <string name="birthyear">Birth Year:\u0020</string>
    <string name="birthmonth">Birth Month:\u0020</string>
    <string name="choosebirthyear">Select Year</string>
    <string name="choosebirthmonth">Select Month</string>
    
    <string name="typecountry">Type to search</string>
    <string name="calcing">Processing</string>
    <string name="calcvalue">Calculated value:\u0020</string>
    <string name="afcresult">Result by Antral-follicle count is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="amhresult">Result by AMH volume is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="ovaresult">Result by Ovarian Volume is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="fshresult">Chance of Live Birth by FSH is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="mmaresult">"Chance of Live Birth by Mother's Menopause Age is:\u0020"</string>
    <string name="ngfresult1">"You have about\u0020"</string>
    <string name="ngfresult2">"\u0020of the eggs you were born with. In 3 years time this percentage is estimated to be:\u0020"</string>
    
    <string name="positive">Positive</string>
    <string name="negative">Negative</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    
    <string name="resvisual">Result Visualization</string>
    <string name="plswait">Please wait....</string>
    <string name="resulttitle">Results</string>
    <string name="result">View Result</string>
    <string name="resultstatus">Status:\u0020</string>
    <string name="resultmessage">No result was generated for the values entered. Please ensure that you have entered valid values and try again.</string>
    <string name="visualizer">Visualizer</string>
    <string name="visualize">Visualize</string>
    <string name="descriptiontitle">Interpretation:\u0020</string>
    
    <string name="afcdescription">Based on the Antral-Follicle count (AFC) result, your status is determined to be at the\u0020</string>
    <string name="percentile">\u0020percentile above the general pouplation mean, as indicated on the gauge above.</string>
    <string name="amhdescription">Based on the Anti-Mullerian Hormone (AMH) result, your status is determined to be at\u0020</string>
    <string name="ovadescription">Based on the Ovarian Volume result, your status is determined to be at\u0020</string>
    <string name="abovemean">\u0020standard deviations above the general population mean, as indicated on the gauge above.</string>
    <string name="belowmean">\u0020standard deviations below the general population mean, as indicated on the gauge above.</string>
    
    <string name="research">You can view the research work in which this calculation is based on\u0020</string>
    <string name="here">here.</string>
    
    <string name="positiverecommendation">\u0020Therefore, based on this result your ovaries are fine, however, it is recommended that you see your doctor for further enquiries about this result.</string>
    <string name="neutralrecommendation">\u0020Therefore, based on this result your ovaries are neutral, however, it is recommended that you see your doctor for further enquiries about this result.</string>
    <string name="negativerecommendation">\u0020Therefore, based on this result your ovaries are not fine, however, it is recommended that you see your doctor for further enquiries about this result.</string>
    
    <string name="privacy">This application sends no information about your answers to any server. Your results are calculated directly on your device. The individualised results generated by MyOvaries is based on works published by renowned Medical practitioners and accredited academic laureates.\u0020</string>
	<string name="privacy2">However, they are not responsible for the individual choices regarding treatment that you make based on the results using MyOvaries. Patients should always discuss their options for treatment with trained clinicians.</string>
	<string name="privacytitle">Privacy Policy</string>
	<string name="paper">paper</string>
	<string name="generaladvice">General Advice</string>
	<string name="general">General</string>
	<string name="average">What is Average?</string>
	<string name="smoking">Smoking</string>
	<string name="bmi">BMI (Height and Weight)</string>
	<string name="genetics">Genetics</string>
	<string name="race">Race</string>
	<string name="parity">Parity</string>
	<string name="sampletext">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto beatae vitae dicta sunt explicabo.</string>
	
	<string name="aboutus">About Us</string>
	<string name="aboutus1">Professor Hamish Wallace MD is the Muirhead Professor of Obstetrics and Gynaecology at the University of Edinburgh and an international expert in IVF.</string>
	<string name="aboutus2">"His research aims to understand and improve the health of women and their offspring throughout their reproductive life span. He is directly involved in looking after patients in Scotlan's two largest and most successful IVF units."</string>
	<string name="aboutus3">Dr Tom Kelsey is a Senior Lecturer at the University of Saint Andrews, and an international expert in mathematical models for biomedicine.</string>
	<string name="aboutus4">Tom, together with his student, were instrumental in developing the smartphone apps.</string>
	<string name="aboutus5">Mr Olalekan Baruwa is a MSc student at the University of Saint Andrews, and a software developer with a solid industrial experience in developing web and mobile applications.</string>
	<string name="aboutus6">Olalekan, worked on this project under the direct supervision of Dr Tom Kelsey.</string>
	<string name="readmore">read more</string>
	
	<string name="summary">Summary</string>
	
	<string name="ok">OK</string>

</resources>
