<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ovary Reserve</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ovaryres">Ovary Reserve</string>
    <string name="empty"></string>
    <string name="age">Age Details</string>
    <string name="medic">Medical Details</string>
    <string name="howold">How Old Are You?</string>
    <string name="iam">I am\u0020</string>
    <string name="and">\u0020and\u0020</string>
    <string name="years">years,</string>
    <string name="months">months.</string>
    <string name="amhvalue">AMH Volume</string>
    <string name="amhhint">Enter your AMH volume</string>
    <string name="volvalue">Ovarian Volume</string>
    <string name="volhint">Enter your Ovarian volume</string>
    <string name="afcvalue">Antral-Follicle Count</string>
    <string name="afchint">Enter your Antral-follicle count</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="info">Information</string>
    <string name="birthyear">Birth Year:\u0020</string>
    <string name="birthmonth">Birth Month:\u0020</string>
    <string name="choosebirthyear">Choose Birth Year</string>
    <string name="choosebirthmonth">Choose Birth Month</string>
    <string name="typecountry">Type to search</string>
    <string name="calcing">Calculating</string>
    <string name="calcvalue">Calculated value:\u0020</string>
    <string name="afcresult">Result by Antral-follicle count is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="amhresult">Result by AMH volume is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="ovaresult">Result by Ovarian Volume is:\u0020</string>
    <string name="positive">Positive</string>
    <string name="negative">Negative</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="plswait">Please wait....</string>
    <string name="resulttitle">No Result</string>
    <string name="resultmessage">No result was generated for the values entered. Please ensure that you have entered valid values and try again.</string>
    <string name="gaugetitle">View Result</string>
    
    <string name="privacy">This application sends no information about your answers to any server. Your results are calculated directly on your device. The individualised prediction generated by IVFpredict is based on the work published in the\u0020</string>
	<string name="privacy2">\u0020by Nelson and Lawlor in PLOS Medicine. They are not responsible for the individual choices regarding treatment that you make based on the calculations using IVFpredict. Patients should always discuss their options for treatment with trained clinicians</string>
	<string name="privacytitle">Privacy Policy</string>
	<string name="paper">paper</string>
	
	<string name="aboutus">About Us</string>
	<string name="aboutus1">Professor Scott Nelson is the Muirhead Professor of Obstetrics and Gynaecology at the University of Glasgow and an international expert in IVF.</string>
	<string name="aboutus2">"His research aims to understand and improve the health of women and their offspring throughout their reproductive life span. He is directly involved in looking after patients in Scotlan's two largest and most successful IVF units."</string>
	<string name="aboutus3">Professor Debbie Lawlor is the Professor of Epidemiology at Bristol University and an international expert in translational research.</string>
	<string name="aboutus4">"Debbie's research is underpinned by her interest in understanding how biological (including genetic), social and environmental exposures from across the life course affect the risk of chronic disease in adulthood and how, therefore, appropriate prevention of these conditions can be achieved."</string>
	<string name="aboutus5">Dr Tom Kelsey is a Senior Lecturer at the University of Saint Andrews, and an international expert in mathematical models for biomedicine.</string>
	<string name="aboutus6">Tom, together with his colleague Dr Chris Jefferson, were instrumental in developing the online calculator and smartphone apps.</string>
	<string name="readmore">read more</string>
	
	<string name="summary">Summary</string>
	
	<string name="ok">OK</string>

</resources>
